KALVIN REZA PRATAMA

BACHELOR OF URBAN AND REGIONAL PLANNING



kalvinpratamarch@gmail.com

Bandar Lampung, Lampung



0896-3372-2724



linkedin.com/in/kpratama

SUMMARY

Urban Planning bachelor certified in computer processing and data analytics. Entry-level data analyst with expertise in database operations using *spreadsheets*, SPSS, SQL, and R. Have strong analytical skills to find schematic patterns and making data-based decisions.

EDUCATION

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA

August 2017 – November 2021

Bachelor of Urban and Regional Planning (S.P.W.K) Graduated with Honors Predicate, GPA 3.72

TRAININGS

FGA DIGITAL TALENT SCHOLARSHIP

September 2022 – November 2022

Program of Dicoding Indonesia in association with Kemenkominfo RI

Google Data Analytics training (Spreadsheet, SQL, RStudio, Tableau) through Coursera

INTRO TO DATA ANALYTICS

August 2022

Program of RevoU Mini Course

Basic data analytics training and insight sharing about data analytics experiences

COMPUTER OPERATOR ASSISTANT

July 2022 – September 2022

Program of Balai Latihan Kerja Bandar Lampung

Training on the operation of computers and their peripheral devices, word processing applications, spreadsheets, and internet-based applications

WORK EXPERIENCES

BAPPEDA PROVINSI LAMPUNG

June 2020 – August 2020

Intern Staff

- Being a helping hand for multiple assignments to assist city/regency governments' annual work plan.
- Created comparison checks for actual provincial dan regencies road lengths compared to documented road lengths.
- Play role as a meeting notetaker in multiple occassions.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

HMP MANDALANATA ITERA

February 2018 – February 2021

- Science and Profession Department Staff 2020 2021
- GIS software instructor that taught new students and mapping learners
- Took part as a member of PHP2D HMP Mandalanata for village empowerment in association with Kemendikbud RI
- Ruang Plano 1.0 Scientific Paper Competition Committee

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

- Bahasa Indonesia (Native)
- English (C2 Proficient)

SOFTWARE MASTERY

Administration

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)

Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides

Data Management & Analysis

- MySQL Community
- **RStudio**
- Google BigQuery

Visualization & Modelling

- AutoCAD
- SketchUp
- Stella/iThink

Geographical Mapping

ArcGIS

Graphic Design

CorelDraw

- **IBM SPSS Statistics**
- **PostgreSQL**
- Tableau Public
- Microsoft Power BI
- **QGIS**

Movavi Video Editor

SKILL CERTIFICATIONS

COMPUTER OPERATOR ASSISTANT

Licensed by Balai Latihan Kerja Bandar Lampung

- Certified as competent in operating computer and its peripheral devices.
- Certified as competent in operating word-based, spreadsheet, and internet-based softwares.

GOOGLE DATA ANALYTICS

Licensed by Coursera

- Completed eight courses, developed by Google, that include practice-based assessments.
- Certified in data analytics tools including spreadsheets, SQL, Tableau, and R.
- Certified in prepare, process, analyze, and share data for data-based decision making.